{"RT_log_version":"1.0.1","RT_log_data":[{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL3.incr.2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549814578738","data":{"timestamp":" 1549814578738"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_190219"," gameId":" null"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" null"," tutorId":" null"," matrixName":" null"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" null"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" null"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549814586241","data":{"timestamp":" 1549814586241"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_190219"," gameId":" null"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" null"," tutorId":" null"," matrixName":" null"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" null"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" null"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd:lc.wrd.len-5.3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549814620474","data":{"timestamp":" 1549814620474"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_190219"," gameId":" c52d19ba-d4df-454e-ae23-687925c49ef2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd_lc.wrd.len-5.3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_sijui"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" s"," userResponse":" s"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd:lc.wrd.len-5.3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549814623616","data":{"timestamp":" 1549814623616"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_190219"," gameId":" c52d19ba-d4df-454e-ae23-687925c49ef2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd_lc.wrd.len-5.3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_sijui"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" i"," userResponse":" i"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd:lc.wrd.len-5.3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549814627249","data":{"timestamp":" 1549814627249"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_190219"," gameId":" c52d19ba-d4df-454e-ae23-687925c49ef2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd_lc.wrd.len-5.3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_sijui"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" j"," userResponse":" j"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd:lc.wrd.len-5.3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549814630091","data":{"timestamp":" 1549814630091"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_190219"," gameId":" c52d19ba-d4df-454e-ae23-687925c49ef2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd_lc.wrd.len-5.3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_sijui"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" u"," userResponse":" u"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd:lc.wrd.len-5.3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549814643931","data":{"timestamp":" 1549814643931"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_190219"," gameId":" c52d19ba-d4df-454e-ae23-687925c49ef2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd_lc.wrd.len-5.3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_sijui"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" i"," userResponse":" i"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd:lc.wrd.len-5.3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549814654391","data":{"timestamp":" 1549814654390"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_190219"," gameId":" c52d19ba-d4df-454e-ae23-687925c49ef2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd_lc.wrd.len-5.3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_rinda"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" r"," userResponse":" r"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd:lc.wrd.len-5.3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549814660764","data":{"timestamp":" 1549814660764"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_190219"," gameId":" c52d19ba-d4df-454e-ae23-687925c49ef2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd_lc.wrd.len-5.3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_rinda"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" i"," userResponse":" i"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd:lc.wrd.len-5.3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549814665123","data":{"timestamp":" 1549814665123"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_190219"," gameId":" c52d19ba-d4df-454e-ae23-687925c49ef2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd_lc.wrd.len-5.3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_rinda"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" n"," userResponse":" n"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd:lc.wrd.len-5.3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549814669307","data":{"timestamp":" 1549814669307"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_190219"," gameId":" c52d19ba-d4df-454e-ae23-687925c49ef2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd_lc.wrd.len-5.3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_rinda"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" d"," userResponse":" d"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd:lc.wrd.len-5.3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549814671346","data":{"timestamp":" 1549814671346"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_190219"," gameId":" c52d19ba-d4df-454e-ae23-687925c49ef2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd_lc.wrd.len-5.3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_rinda"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" a"," userResponse":" a"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd:lc.wrd.len-5.3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549814685663","data":{"timestamp":" 1549814685663"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_190219"," gameId":" c52d19ba-d4df-454e-ae23-687925c49ef2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd_lc.wrd.len-5.3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_mumeo"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" m"," userResponse":" m"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd:lc.wrd.len-5.3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549814688496","data":{"timestamp":" 1549814688496"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_190219"," gameId":" c52d19ba-d4df-454e-ae23-687925c49ef2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd_lc.wrd.len-5.3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_mumeo"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" u"," userResponse":" u"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd:lc.wrd.len-5.3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549814695019","data":{"timestamp":" 1549814695019"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_190219"," gameId":" c52d19ba-d4df-454e-ae23-687925c49ef2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd_lc.wrd.len-5.3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_mumeo"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" m"," userResponse":" m"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd:lc.wrd.len-5.3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549814699162","data":{"timestamp":" 1549814699162"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_190219"," gameId":" c52d19ba-d4df-454e-ae23-687925c49ef2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd_lc.wrd.len-5.3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_mumeo"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" e"," userResponse":" e"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd:lc.wrd.len-5.3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549814702268","data":{"timestamp":" 1549814702268"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_190219"," gameId":" c52d19ba-d4df-454e-ae23-687925c49ef2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd_lc.wrd.len-5.3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_mumeo"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" o"," userResponse":" o"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd:lc.wrd.len-5.3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549814712103","data":{"timestamp":" 1549814712103"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_190219"," gameId":" c52d19ba-d4df-454e-ae23-687925c49ef2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd_lc.wrd.len-5.3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_mwezi"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" m"," userResponse":" m"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_METRIC"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd:lc.wrd.len-5.3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549814721023","data":{"timestamp":" 1549814721023"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_190219"," gameId":" c52d19ba-d4df-454e-ae23-687925c49ef2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd_lc.wrd.len-5.3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_mwezi"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" m"," userResponse":" m"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd:lc.wrd.len-5.3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549814726014","data":{"timestamp":" 1549814726014"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_190219"," gameId":" c52d19ba-d4df-454e-ae23-687925c49ef2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd_lc.wrd.len-5.3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_mwezi"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" w"," userResponse":" w"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd:lc.wrd.len-5.3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549814729932","data":{"timestamp":" 1549814729932"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_190219"," gameId":" c52d19ba-d4df-454e-ae23-687925c49ef2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd_lc.wrd.len-5.3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_mwezi"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" e"," userResponse":" e"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd:lc.wrd.len-5.3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549814735085","data":{"timestamp":" 1549814735085"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_190219"," gameId":" c52d19ba-d4df-454e-ae23-687925c49ef2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd_lc.wrd.len-5.3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_mwezi"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" z"," userResponse":" z"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd:lc.wrd.len-5.3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549814737903","data":{"timestamp":" 1549814737903"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_190219"," gameId":" c52d19ba-d4df-454e-ae23-687925c49ef2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd_lc.wrd.len-5.3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_mwezi"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" i"," userResponse":" L"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_CHAR"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd:lc.wrd.len-5.3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549814743517","data":{"timestamp":" 1549814743517"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_190219"," gameId":" c52d19ba-d4df-454e-ae23-687925c49ef2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd_lc.wrd.len-5.3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_mwezi"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" i"," userResponse":" i"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd:lc.wrd.len-5.3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549814759712","data":{"timestamp":" 1549814759712"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_190219"," gameId":" c52d19ba-d4df-454e-ae23-687925c49ef2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd_lc.wrd.len-5.3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_ngozi"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" n"," userResponse":" n"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd:lc.wrd.len-5.3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549814765730","data":{"timestamp":" 1549814765730"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_190219"," gameId":" c52d19ba-d4df-454e-ae23-687925c49ef2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd_lc.wrd.len-5.3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_ngozi"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" g"," userResponse":" g"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd:lc.wrd.len-5.3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549814769113","data":{"timestamp":" 1549814769113"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_190219"," gameId":" c52d19ba-d4df-454e-ae23-687925c49ef2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd_lc.wrd.len-5.3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_ngozi"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" o"," userResponse":" o"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd:lc.wrd.len-5.3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549814773331","data":{"timestamp":" 1549814773331"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_190219"," gameId":" c52d19ba-d4df-454e-ae23-687925c49ef2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd_lc.wrd.len-5.3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_ngozi"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" z"," userResponse":" z"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd:lc.wrd.len-5.3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549814776205","data":{"timestamp":" 1549814776205"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_190219"," gameId":" c52d19ba-d4df-454e-ae23-687925c49ef2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd_lc.wrd.len-5.3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_ngozi"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" i"," userResponse":" u"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_CHAR"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd:lc.wrd.len-5.3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549814784629","data":{"timestamp":" 1549814784629"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_190219"," gameId":" c52d19ba-d4df-454e-ae23-687925c49ef2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd_lc.wrd.len-5.3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_ngozi"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" i"," userResponse":" i"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd:lc.wrd.len-5.3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549814805535","data":{"timestamp":" 1549814805534"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_190219"," gameId":" c52d19ba-d4df-454e-ae23-687925c49ef2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd_lc.wrd.len-5.3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_baada"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" b"," userResponse":" b"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd:lc.wrd.len-5.3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549814810152","data":{"timestamp":" 1549814810152"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_190219"," gameId":" c52d19ba-d4df-454e-ae23-687925c49ef2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd_lc.wrd.len-5.3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_baada"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" a"," userResponse":" a"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd:lc.wrd.len-5.3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549814813369","data":{"timestamp":" 1549814813369"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_190219"," gameId":" c52d19ba-d4df-454e-ae23-687925c49ef2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd_lc.wrd.len-5.3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_baada"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" a"," userResponse":" a"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd:lc.wrd.len-5.3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549814820950","data":{"timestamp":" 1549814820950"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_190219"," gameId":" c52d19ba-d4df-454e-ae23-687925c49ef2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd_lc.wrd.len-5.3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_baada"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" d"," userResponse":" d"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd:lc.wrd.len-5.3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549814823371","data":{"timestamp":" 1549814823371"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_190219"," gameId":" c52d19ba-d4df-454e-ae23-687925c49ef2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd_lc.wrd.len-5.3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_baada"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" a"," userResponse":" a"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd:lc.wrd.len-5.3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549814835659","data":{"timestamp":" 1549814835659"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_190219"," gameId":" c52d19ba-d4df-454e-ae23-687925c49ef2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd_lc.wrd.len-5.3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_ngoma"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" n"," userResponse":" n"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd:lc.wrd.len-5.3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549814841244","data":{"timestamp":" 1549814841244"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_190219"," gameId":" c52d19ba-d4df-454e-ae23-687925c49ef2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd_lc.wrd.len-5.3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_ngoma"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" g"," userResponse":" 9"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_CHAR"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd:lc.wrd.len-5.3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549814848063","data":{"timestamp":" 1549814848063"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_190219"," gameId":" c52d19ba-d4df-454e-ae23-687925c49ef2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd_lc.wrd.len-5.3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_ngoma"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" g"," userResponse":" 9"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_CHAR"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd:lc.wrd.len-5.3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549814855219","data":{"timestamp":" 1549814855219"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_190219"," gameId":" c52d19ba-d4df-454e-ae23-687925c49ef2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd_lc.wrd.len-5.3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_ngoma"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" g"," userResponse":" 9"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_CHAR"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd:lc.wrd.len-5.3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549814863859","data":{"timestamp":" 1549814863859"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_190219"," gameId":" c52d19ba-d4df-454e-ae23-687925c49ef2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd_lc.wrd.len-5.3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_ngoma"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" g"," userResponse":" 9"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_METRIC - FTR_ERROR_CHAR"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd:lc.wrd.len-5.3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549814872481","data":{"timestamp":" 1549814872481"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_190219"," gameId":" c52d19ba-d4df-454e-ae23-687925c49ef2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd_lc.wrd.len-5.3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_ngoma"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" g"," userResponse":" g"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd:lc.wrd.len-5.3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549814875854","data":{"timestamp":" 1549814875854"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_190219"," gameId":" c52d19ba-d4df-454e-ae23-687925c49ef2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd_lc.wrd.len-5.3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_ngoma"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" o"," userResponse":" o"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd:lc.wrd.len-5.3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549814879195","data":{"timestamp":" 1549814879194"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_190219"," gameId":" c52d19ba-d4df-454e-ae23-687925c49ef2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd_lc.wrd.len-5.3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_ngoma"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" m"," userResponse":" m"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd:lc.wrd.len-5.3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549814881662","data":{"timestamp":" 1549814881662"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_190219"," gameId":" c52d19ba-d4df-454e-ae23-687925c49ef2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd_lc.wrd.len-5.3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_ngoma"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" a"," userResponse":" a"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd:lc.wrd.len-5.3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549814909562","data":{"timestamp":" 1549814909562"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_190219"," gameId":" c52d19ba-d4df-454e-ae23-687925c49ef2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd_lc.wrd.len-5.3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_nyani"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" n"," userResponse":" n"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd:lc.wrd.len-5.3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549814913924","data":{"timestamp":" 1549814913924"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_190219"," gameId":" c52d19ba-d4df-454e-ae23-687925c49ef2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd_lc.wrd.len-5.3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_nyani"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" y"," userResponse":" y"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd:lc.wrd.len-5.3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549814917245","data":{"timestamp":" 1549814917245"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_190219"," gameId":" c52d19ba-d4df-454e-ae23-687925c49ef2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd_lc.wrd.len-5.3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_nyani"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" a"," userResponse":" a"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd:lc.wrd.len-5.3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549814921131","data":{"timestamp":" 1549814921131"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_190219"," gameId":" c52d19ba-d4df-454e-ae23-687925c49ef2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd_lc.wrd.len-5.3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_nyani"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" n"," userResponse":" n"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd:lc.wrd.len-5.3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549814923689","data":{"timestamp":" 1549814923688"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_190219"," gameId":" c52d19ba-d4df-454e-ae23-687925c49ef2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd_lc.wrd.len-5.3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_nyani"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" i"," userResponse":" i"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd:lc.wrd.len-5.3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549814942545","data":{"timestamp":" 1549814942545"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_190219"," gameId":" c52d19ba-d4df-454e-ae23-687925c49ef2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd_lc.wrd.len-5.3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_panya"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" p"," userResponse":" p"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd:lc.wrd.len-5.3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549814950946","data":{"timestamp":" 1549814950946"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_190219"," gameId":" c52d19ba-d4df-454e-ae23-687925c49ef2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd_lc.wrd.len-5.3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_panya"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" a"," userResponse":" a"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd:lc.wrd.len-5.3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549814954883","data":{"timestamp":" 1549814954883"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_190219"," gameId":" c52d19ba-d4df-454e-ae23-687925c49ef2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd_lc.wrd.len-5.3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_panya"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" n"," userResponse":" n"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd:lc.wrd.len-5.3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549814958190","data":{"timestamp":" 1549814958190"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_190219"," gameId":" c52d19ba-d4df-454e-ae23-687925c49ef2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd_lc.wrd.len-5.3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_panya"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" y"," userResponse":" y"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd:lc.wrd.len-5.3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549814961122","data":{"timestamp":" 1549814961122"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_190219"," gameId":" c52d19ba-d4df-454e-ae23-687925c49ef2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd_lc.wrd.len-5.3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_panya"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" a"," userResponse":" a"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd:lc.wrd.len-5.3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549814972119","data":{"timestamp":" 1549814972119"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_190219"," gameId":" c52d19ba-d4df-454e-ae23-687925c49ef2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd_lc.wrd.len-5.3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_meusi"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" m"," userResponse":" m"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd:lc.wrd.len-5.3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549814977222","data":{"timestamp":" 1549814977222"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_190219"," gameId":" c52d19ba-d4df-454e-ae23-687925c49ef2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd_lc.wrd.len-5.3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_meusi"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" e"," userResponse":" e"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd:lc.wrd.len-5.3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549814980670","data":{"timestamp":" 1549814980670"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_190219"," gameId":" c52d19ba-d4df-454e-ae23-687925c49ef2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd_lc.wrd.len-5.3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_meusi"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" u"," userResponse":" u"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd:lc.wrd.len-5.3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549814984804","data":{"timestamp":" 1549814984804"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_190219"," gameId":" c52d19ba-d4df-454e-ae23-687925c49ef2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd_lc.wrd.len-5.3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_meusi"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" s"," userResponse":" s"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd:lc.wrd.len-5.3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549814988236","data":{"timestamp":" 1549814988236"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_190219"," gameId":" c52d19ba-d4df-454e-ae23-687925c49ef2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd_lc.wrd.len-5.3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_meusi"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" i"," userResponse":" i"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd:lc.wrd.len-5.3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549814997519","data":{"timestamp":" 1549814997519"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_190219"," gameId":" c52d19ba-d4df-454e-ae23-687925c49ef2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd_lc.wrd.len-5.3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" write_meusi"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL4.incr.1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549815017986","data":{"timestamp":" 1549815017986"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_190219"," gameId":" c52d19ba-d4df-454e-ae23-687925c49ef2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd_lc.wrd.len-5.3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" write_meusi"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd.dic:lc.wrd.len-5.4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549815027821","data":{"timestamp":" 1549815027821"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_190219"," gameId":" c52d19ba-d4df-454e-ae23-687925c49ef2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd_lc.wrd.len-5.3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" write_meusi"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549815032285","data":{"timestamp":" 1549815032285"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_190219"," gameId":" c52d19ba-d4df-454e-ae23-687925c49ef2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd_lc.wrd.len-5.3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" write_meusi"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_18","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549815039417","data":{"timestamp":" 1549815039416"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_190219"," gameId":" c52d19ba-d4df-454e-ae23-687925c49ef2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd_lc.wrd.len-5.3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" write_meusi"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"num.scale:0..10.off1.1__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549815044650","data":{"timestamp":" 1549815044649"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_190219"," gameId":" c52d19ba-d4df-454e-ae23-687925c49ef2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd_lc.wrd.len-5.3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" write_meusi"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:0.1.2.init.s","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549815060636","data":{"timestamp":" 1549815060636"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_190219"," gameId":" c52d19ba-d4df-454e-ae23-687925c49ef2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd_lc.wrd.len-5.3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" write_meusi"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"end":"end"}]}